Thank you, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)You're welcome.
Point of inquiry: Why did you
put your car key in the door lock?
(Penny:)I'll tell you why.
Today I had an audition.
(Penny:)It took me two hours to get there.
I waited an hour for my turn.
Before I could start, they told me
I look too Midwest for the part.
(Penny:)Too Midwest.
What the hell does that even mean?
(Sheldon:)The American Midwest was mostly settled
by Scandinavian and Germanic peoples...
- ...who have characteristic facial...
- I know what it means.
God, I have been in L.A.
for almost two years now.
I haven't gotten a single acting job.
I've accomplished nothing.
(Penny:)Haven't gotten a raise at work.
Haven't even had sex in six months.
And when I was walking up those stairs
a fly flew in my mouth and I ate it.
(Sheldon:)Well, actually, insects are a dietary staple
in many cultures.
(Sheldon:)They're almost pure protein.
Oh, son of a bitch.
(Sheldon:)The condensation on your frozen foods...
(Sheldon:)...weakened the structural integrity
of the bag.